        <attribute>
            <name>preserveDataModel</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Indicates whether the state of the whole DataModel should be saved and
                restored. When set to false, the value-binding for the "value" attribute
                of this table is executed each time the page is rendered. When set to 
                true, that value-binding is only executed when the component is first
                created, and the DataModel state is thereafter saved/restored automatically
                by the component.
                
                When column sorting is used for a table this property needs to be false
                so that the DataModel can be updated to reflect any changes in the
                sort criteria.
                
                Default: false
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>preserveRowStates</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Indicates whether the state for each row should not be discarded before 
                the datatable is rendered again. Setting this to true might be hepful if
                an input component inside the datatable has no valuebinding and the value
                entered in there should be displayed again. 
                This will only work reliable if the datamodel of the datatable did not change
                either by sorting, removing or adding rows.
                                
                Default: false 
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>forceIdIndexFormula</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
				A formula that overrides the default row index in the construction of table's
				body components.
				Example : #{myRowVar.key}
				Warning, the EL should evaluate to a unique value for each row !
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>sortColumn</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Value reference to a model property that gives the current sort column name.
                The target String property is set to the "columnName" of whichever column has been
                chosen to sort by, and the method which is bound to the "value" attribute
                of this table (ie which provides the DataModel used) is expected to use this
                property to determine how to sort the DataModel's contents.
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>sortAscending</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Value reference to a model property that gives the current sort direction.
                The target Boolean property is set to true when the selected sortColumn
                should be sorted in ascending order, and false otherwise. The method which
                is bound to the "value" attribute of this table (ie which provides the DataModel
                used) is expected to use this property to determine how to sort the DataModel's
                contents.
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>preserveSort</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Indicates whether the state of the sortColumn and sortAscending attribute
                should be saved and restored and written back to the model during the
                update model phase.
                Default: true
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>renderedIfEmpty</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Indicates whether this table should be rendered if the underlying DataModel is
                empty.
                You could as well use rendered="#{not empty bean.list}", but this one causes
                the getList method of your model bean beeing called up to five times per
                request, which is not optimal when the list is backed by a DB table.
                Using renderedIfEmpty="false" solves this problem, because the MyFaces
                extended HtmlDataTable automatically caches the DataModel and calles the
                model getter only once per request.
                Default: true
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowIndexVar</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                A parameter name, under which the current rowIndex is set in request scope
                similar to the var parameter.
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowCountVar</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                A parameter name, under which the rowCount is set in request scope
                similar to the var parameter.
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>previousRowDataVar</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                A parameter name, under which the previous RowData Object is set in request scope
                similar to the rowIndexVar and rowCountVar parameters.
                Mind that the value of this request scope attribute is null in the first row
                or when isRowAvailable returns false for the previous row.
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowOnClick</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Defines a JavaScript onclick event handler for each table row
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowOnDblClick</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Defines a JavaScript ondblclick event handler for each table row
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowOnMouseDown</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Defines a JavaScript onmpusedown event handler for each table row
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowOnMouseUp</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Defines a JavaScript onmouseup event handler for each table row
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowOnMouseOver</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Defines a JavaScript onmouseover event handler for each table row
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowOnMouseMove</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Defines a JavaScript onmousemove event handler for each table row
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowOnMouseOut</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Defines a JavaScript onmouseout event handler for each table row
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowOnKeyPress</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Defines a JavaScript onkeypress event handler for each table row
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowOnKeyDown</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Defines a JavaScript onkeydown event handler for each table row
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowOnKeyUp</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                Defines a JavaScript onkeyup event handler for each table row
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowId</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>
                The id to use for &lt;tr> elements that are generated by the table.
            </description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowStyleClass</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>Corresponds to the HTML class attribute for the row tr tag.</description>
        </attribute>
        <attribute>
            <name>rowStyle</name>
            <required>false</required>
            <rtexprvalue>false</rtexprvalue>
            <description>Corresponds to the HTML style attribute for the row tr tag.</description>
        </attribute>